hotel.net 2015-04-26

# Corporate | Privacy Policy | Hotel.net

World Media Group, LLC ("Company") manages websites including the Hotel.net website ("Website") and provides this Privacy Policy because we value your right to privacy.

This Policy is effective as of September 30, 2011 and governs the collection of personal information through our Website on or after this date. This Policy describes the types of information we may collect from visitors and how that information is used. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully before providing us with any personal information. If you have any questions or concerns about this Policy, please know that we will handle your requests with care. You may Contact Us at any time to discuss this Privacy Policy.

## Information We Collect From Unregistered Users

Unregistered Users are users that visit our Website and have not signed up for an account at our Website for the purpose of using one or more of our services or have not engaged in services at our Website where the user has provided us with personal information. The information we collect from unregistered users is limited. We log your IP address in order to help diagnose problems with our server, administer our Website, and to track usage statistics. Your IP address may vary each time you visit, or it may stay the same. We may log other non-personal information such as the type of internet browser that you use or your connection speed. It would be extremely difficult for us to identify you through your IP address, browser type, or other non-personal information that we collect and we make no attempt to do so.

From time to time our Website also may run usability testing to help us improve the functions of the site for all users.  This may include recording random sessions that track users' actions and movements on specific pages of the Website.  We set up our usability tests to be anonymous and therefore we do not record fields that have personally identifiable information entered by users and we do not store the user's IP connected to such tests.  Our tests are also contained to our Website and we do not track user's behavior on other websites.  If you would like to opt out of these usability tests you may do so by visiting <http://mouseflow.com/opt-out>.

If you reached our Website by clicking on a link or advertisement on another website, we may log that information as well. We may place a small "cookie" file on your computer's hard drive. A cookie may contain information that allows us to track your path through our Website and to determine whether you have visited us before. You may elect not to accept cookies by changing settings in your browser; however, by not accepting cookies some or all of the functions of our Website may not work for you.

Unless you register with us, cookies we place on your computer will not contain personally identifiable information. We may use cookies to help us understand how visitors use our Website, and to help us to improve our Website. We also compile this information and use it in the aggregate to determine common themes among our visitors or trends which we can use to improve the service to our users.

## Information We Collect From Registered Users

Registered Users are users that sign up for an account at our Website for the purpose of using one or more of our services or that use our services and in doing so provide us with personal information. You can register at our Website to take advantage of personalization features as well as other services that we offer. If you choose to register with us, it may allow you access to unique features of our Website. By registering you can receive notification of new services or changes in services that we offer.

If you register with us, we will collect personal information from you that you enter into our forms in addition to the non-personal information described above that we collect from unregistered users. Such personal information may include information about you such as name, email address, mailing address, telephone number, username and password, and contact information. The information we collect may vary. We may store all or some of this information such as your login user name in a cookie file on your hard drive so that our system will recognize you each time you visit our Website. In that way, we can save your preferences between visits and present you with a customized Website each time you visit. If you reach our Website through one of our partners and you choose to register with us, we may be required to give our partner your registration information. If you visit one of our partner sites and register or purchase travel or other services or goods with them while they are acting as a service provider to us then they will have access to the personal information that you provide to them. Partners use of your personal information will be governed by their privacy policy.

Additionally, authorized personnel may update your registration information to accurately reflect any new information included in communications received from you.

## How We Use The Personal Information We Collect

Your information allows us to personalize our Web site so that it is most useful to you. It may allow you to log into our site automatically each time you visit, rather than manually typing your user name and password every time. We may use your personal information to periodically contact you with news or important information, to provide you with other information or invitations related to your membership, and to request your feedback on our site. For instance when you purchase travel or other services or goods from us we will send you travel booking or other relevant confirmations relating to your order. In addition, we send our customers and registered users periodic newsletters as well as valuable travel specials and other offers such as a special on a dream vacation, low cost airfare rates or relevant deals that we have secured for our users. We can use the information that you give us to make our specials more relevant to you. While many of our users look forward to receiving such offers, if you decide for any reason to not receive newsletters or special offers from us you can opt-out at any time by letting us know (opt-out links are provided in all emails). If you change your mind then just opt back in by letting us know. 

## Disclosure Of Your Personal Information To Other Parties

We may share some of your personally identifiable information with our parent company and subsidiaries or with entities engaged in providing services to us where the sharing of information is needed as part of the provision of services. We also may share your information in connection with a corporate transaction, such as a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, and in the unlikely event of bankruptcy. We require such parties to agree to use any such personally-identifiable data solely for the purpose of providing the specified services we have requested from them or solely for the purpose of providing the services that you have requested from us. These entities or other parties must abide by the same provisions of the Privacy Policy and also comply with applicable laws governing the transmission of promotional communications.

## Disclosure Of Your Personal Information If Required By Law

We cooperate with legal authorities, and may in some circumstances be required to disclose personally identifiable information in response to requests from law enforcement authorities, or in response to a subpoena or other legal process. We may turn over information about you if we believe we must in order to prevent a violation of the law.

You also consent to our disclosing information about you in the course of legal proceedings if we are legally required to do so, if we reasonably believe that doing so may mitigate our liability, or if doing so will assist us in enforcing our legal rights.

## Changes To Our Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy should we deem it advisable to do so.

If we make material changes that will affect personal information we have already collected from you, we will make every reasonable effort to notify you of the changes, and to give you the opportunity to amend or cancel your registration. We take your privacy seriously; please don't hesitate to Contact Us with any questions or concerns you may have.
